Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES, 1921-80 (Part 1)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES (part 1)
  - 1.42 PPWP Standing Committees
    - 1.43 Advisory, Special and Other Committees
      - Ad Hoc Committees
        - Claims Review Committee, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 45)
        - Clergyman's Advisory Committee (Revitalized), 1966-70 (Box 37, Folder 46)
        - Clergyman's and Laymen's Advisory Committee, Minutes, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 47)
        - Clergymen's National Advisory Committee
          - 1959-61 (Box 37, Folder 48)
          - Membership Lists, 1959-60 (Box 37, Folder 49)
        - Commerce and Industry Committee
          - Correspondence, 1967-72 (Box 37, Folder 50)
          - Membership List, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 51)
        - Consumer Loan Fund Review Committee, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 52)
        - Executive Directors Advisory Committee to the CEO, 1971-72 (Box 37, Folder 53)
        - FPIA Steering Committee, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 54)
        - International Affairs Committee, Minutes, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 55)
        - Internship Committee, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 56)
        - Legal Advisory Committee, 1955-66 (Box 37, Folder 57)
        - Long Range Planning Committee, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 58)
        - National Advisory Committee on Sex Education, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 59)
        - National Development Council, Member List, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 60)
        - National Training Advisory Committee, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 61)
        - PPWP, PPFA and AGI Negotiating Committee, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 62)
        - Population Dialogue Committee, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 63)
        - Population Education Committee, Population Growth and Family Planning: A Review of the Literature, April 24, 1970, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 64)
        - Presidential Evaluation Committee, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 65)
        - Program Review Committee
          - Correspondence, Memos, 1971-72 (Box 37, Folder 66)
          - Minutes, 1971-73 (Box 37, Folder 67)
        - Sanger Centennial Committee, Minutes, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 68)
        - Regional Representatives
          - 1969-74 (Box 37, Folder 69)
          - 1974-80 (Box 37)
          - Dues Formula, 1970-71 (Box 37, Folder 70)
          - Member Lists
            - 1973-74 (Box 37, Folder 71)
            - 1975-80 (Box 37)
          - North Atlantic Region Council Treasurer, Correspondence from 1978, Dec. 1977, 1977-80 (Box 37, Folder 72)
          - Minutes
            - 1972-74 (Box 37, Folder 73)
            - 1975-80 (Box 37)
        - Religious Affairs Committee
          - A Brief History of PPWP's Religious Affairs Activities, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 74)
          - Abortion
            - 1970-74 (Box 37, Folder 75)
            - l975-77 (Box 37)
          - Contraception and Abortion as Moral Issues, Bruce Galloway, Chairman, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 76)
          - Correspondence and Memos
            - 1976-78 (Box 38, Folder 1)
            - 1972-74 (Box 38, Folder 2)
            - 1975 (Box 38)
          - Conference, Sexism: The Price and Penalty in Family Planning and Religion, 11/2/73, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 3)
          - Correspondence and Memos, 1970-72 (Box 38, Folder 4)
          - Euthanasia, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 5)
          - Family Life Sunday, May 1973, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 6)
          - Form Letters, 1976-79 (Box 38, Folder 7)
          - Guidelines for Affiliate Religious Affairs Committees
            - 1977 (Box 38, Folder 8)
            - Draft, 1976, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 9)
          - Member lists
            - 1971-74 (Box 38, Folder 10)
            - 1975-78 (Box 38)
          - Minutes
            - 1970-74 (Box 38, Folder 11)
            - 1975-78 (Box 38)
          - Planned Parenthood Sunday, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 12)
          - Proposal for Family Planning Through Religious, Social Action Programs, 1974-75 (Box 38, Folder 13)
          - Religious Affairs Booklet, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 14)
          - Report of Religion and Family Planning Conference, Yale Univ. Divinity School, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 15)
          - Sterilization, 1976-78 (Box 38, Folder 16)
        - Scientific Council
          - General, 1957-63 (Box 38, Folder 17)
          - Correspondence, 1957-59 (Box 38, Folder 18)
        - Search Committee for a New President for PPFA
          - 1977 (Box 38, Folder 19)
        - Affiliate Comments, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 20)
          - 1974 (Box 38, Folder 21)
          - 1975 (Box 38)
        - Social Science Committee
          - Correspondence, 1969-74 (Box 38, Folder 22)
          - Minutes
            - 1970-71 (Box 38, Folder 23)
            - 1962-67 (Box 38, Folder 24)
          - Family Planning and Population Education Proposed Guidelines for Integration, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 25)
        - SOP Subcommittee on Educational Affiliates, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 26)
        - Staff Population Education Committee (Formerly Population Dialogue Committee), Correspondence, 1969-71 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Task Forces
      - Task Force, Data Base Questionnaire, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 28)
      - Adolescent Services Task Force, Report, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 29)
      - Task Force on the Role of the Fed. from November 15, 1979, Report, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 30)
      - Fund Raising Task Force
        - Minutes, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 31)
        - Proposal and Report, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 32)
      - Task Force Groups, Member List, 1979-80 (Box 38, Folder 33)
      - Recommendations of PP Task Force on Certification for Sex Education, March 20, 1975, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 34)
      - Task Force on PPFA Education Policy, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 35)
      - Citizen Task Force Activist Mailing, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 36)
      - Task Force on Grant Related Income, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 37)
      - Comprehensive National Public Affairs and Media Program Membership List, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 38)
      - Task Force on Public Impact
        - 1979 (Box 38, Folder 39)
        - Minutes, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 40)
        - Public Affairs Advocacy Program Questionnaires, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 41)
      - Task Force Member, Affiliate Development Task Force, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 42)
      - Task Force on What the Federation Does for Affiliates, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 43)
      - Task Force Recommendation, Weighted Voting Task Force, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 44)
      - White House Conference on Families, Task Force, undated [circa 1980] (Box 38, Folder 45)
    - 1.44 Committees Related to PPWP
      - Executive Directors Council Mexdico
        - 1970-74 (Box 38, Folder 46)
        - 1975-78 (Box 38)
        - 1968-69 (Box 38, Folder 47)
        - Federation Management Information System, Status Report and Questionnaire, 3/10/77, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 48)
        - General Correspondence, 1965-68 (Box 38, Folder 49-50)
        - Background Material for Minneapolis Meeting, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 51)
        - Membership Lists (Mexdico)
          - 1966-74 (Box 38, Folder 52)
          - 1975-77 (Box 38)
        - Evaluation of Minneapolis Meeting, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 53)
        - Mimeo Memos, 1967-70 (Box 38, Folder 54)
        - Minutes, 1967-70 (Box 38, Folder 55)
        - Steering Committee Minutes
          - 1969-74 (Box 38, Folder 56)
          - 1975-77 (Box 38)
        - Mexdico, Minutes, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 57)
        - Mexdico, Papers, 1975-80 (Box 38, Folder 58)
        - Profiles of Affiliate Members, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 1)
        - Reports, General, 1967-69 (Box 39, Folder 2)
        - Mexdico, Report of the Study Committee on Statewide Affiliates and Working Paper, 1972-73 (Box 39, Folder 3)
        - Strengthening the Federation, A Position Paper of Mexdico, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - National Executive Directors Council
        - Legal (Paul, E.), Accounting (Diaz, A.), 1978 (Box 39, Folder 5)
          - 1972-74 (Box 39, Folder 6)
          - 1975-77 (Box 39)
        - Committee Member Lists, 1976-78 (Box 39, Folder 7)
        - Functional Values Questionnaire, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 8)
        - Guidelines for the Evaluation of the Affiliate Executive Director
          - Atlanta, GA, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 9)
          - 1976 (Box 39, Folder 10)
        - Minutes
          - 1972-74 (Box 39, Folder 11)
          - 1975-77 (Box 39)
        - Papers, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 12)
        - NEDC Personnel Practices Survey, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 13)
        - A Profile of PP Executive Directors, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 14)
        - Proposal for Executive Directors' Orientation Program, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 15)
        - Regulations and Procedures, 1973-74 (Box 39, Folder 16)
        - National Executive Directors Council Committee, 1971-72 (Box 39, Folder 17)
        - Steering Committee, 1973-74 (Box 39, Folder 18)
        - Survey of Executive Directors, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - 1.44 Regional Councils, [out] (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - 1.45 Volunteers
    - 1951-74 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - 1975-77 (Box 39)
  - Annual Meeting
    - Minutes, 1956-60 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Annual meeting committee
      - Minutes, 1969-71 (Box 39, Folder 23)
      - Questionnaire: A Critical Look, 1979-80 (Box 39, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence
        - 1969 (Box 39, Folder 25)
        - 1970-74 (Box 39, Folder 26)
        - 1975-79 (Box 39)
      - Member Lists
        - 1960-74 (Box 39, Folder 27)
        - 1975-80 (Box 39)
    - Annual Membership Meeting, Denver, Colorado, Oct. 1980, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - 1979
      - General Correspondence, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 29)
      - Membership Meeting, Nov. 16-17, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 30)
      - General, Forms, Lists, Memos, Programs, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 31)
      - PPFA Women's Caucus Annual Meeting, November 16, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 32)
      - News Alerts, Press Releases, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - 1980, Announcement, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - 1978
      - General Correspondence, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 35)
      - Education, The Federation and The Future, October 23-24, PP Educators' Meeting, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 36)
      - Education Workshop, Nov. 14, 1978, 1978-79 (Box 39, Folder 37)
      - Insurance Sub-Committee Meeting, 10/25, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 38)
      - Medical Committee Meeting, Data Systems, 10/24, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 39)
      - Membership, Minutes, Oct. 27-28, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - 1979, Legal Issues Workshop, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 41)
    - 1978
      - The Morning After, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 42)
      - Regional Council Meeting, Oct. 26, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 43)
      - Workshop on Litigation Strategy, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 44)
      - Summary of Income and Expenses, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 45)
      - General, Forms, Lists, Memos, Programs, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 46)
    - Annual Meeting 1977
      - Film Festival, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 47)
      - Implementation of Surgical Services Workshop, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 48)
      - "Know Your Opposition" Workshop, Religions and Community Affairs, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 49)
      - Membership Meeting, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 50)
      - The Morning After, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 51)
      - Papers, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 52)
      - Workshops, Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 53)
      - General: Forms, Lists, Memos, Programs, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 54)
      - AAPPP-See Their File, October 27-28 (Empty) (Box 39, Folder 55)
    - Annual Meeting 1976
      - Membership Meeting, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 56)
      - Board of Directors Meeting, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 57)
      - Community Affairs, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 58)
      - International Scene: Policies, Programs and PP, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 59)
      - The Morning After, Reporting Daily on the PPFA Annual Meeting, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 60)
      - Professional Staff Day, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 61)
      - Religious Affairs Committee, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 62)
      - Women's Caucus, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 63)
      - Workshops, Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 64)
      - General: Lists, Memos, Programs, Forms, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 65)
      - Regional Council Meeting, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 66)
    - Annual Meeting 1975
      - General Correspondence, 1975-76 (Box 39, Folder 67)
      - Board of Directors, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 68)
      - Membership Meeting, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 69)
      - The Morning After, Reporting Daily on the Annual Meeting, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 70)
      - Remarks to the Membership, Hichock [sic: Hitchcock], 1975 (Box 39, Folder 71)
      - Religious Affairs Committee Workshop, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 72)
      - Workshops, Resources, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 73)
      - General: Lists, Memos, Programs, Forms, etc., 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meeting 1974
      - Affiliation Committee, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Resources, Workshops, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Membership Meeting, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Professional Staff Day, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Regional Council Meetings, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - General: Lists, Memos, Programs, Forms, etc., 1974 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Annual Meeting 1973
      - I & E Committee Meetings, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Membership Meeting, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - PP Attorneys, 1973-74 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Presentations
        - Dr. Allan C. Barnes, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 11)
        - Dr. A. F. Guttmacher, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 12)
        - Dr. Margaret Mead, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 13)
        - Senator Packwood, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - Press Releases, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 15)
      - Professional Day, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - Workshop for Affiliate and Chapter Presidents, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 17)
      - Workshop on Human Sexuality, Sex Education, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 18)
      - Miscellaneous Workshops, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 19)
      - General: Lists, Memos, Programs, Forms, etc., 1973 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Annual Meeting 1972
      - General Correspondence, 1971-72 (Box 40, Folder 21)
      - Comprehensive Family Planning: A Report from the Expansion and Policy Committee, undated (Box 40, Folder 22)
      - Membership Meeting, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - PP Attorneys' Meeting, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 24)
      - Press Coverage, 1971-72 (Box 40, Folder 25)
      - Speeches, 1971-72 (Box 40, Folder 26)
      - Press Releases, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 27)
      - Rap Sessions with PPFA Staff, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 28)
      - General: Lists, Memos, Programs, Forms, etc., 1972-73 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Annual Meeting 1971
      - Board of Directors, 1971-72 (Box 40, Folder 30)
      - Community Affairs Committee, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 31)
      - Five Year Plan, Voting Record Summary, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 32)
      - Minutes of the Great Lakes Region Council Meeting, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 33)
      - Midwest Regional Council Meeting, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 34)
      - Press, Radio and T.V. Coverage, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 35)
      - Program Review, Evaluation, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 36)
      - About the Implications of the 1971 Annual Meeting, Dorothy Millstone, undated (Box 40, Folder 37)
      - Report to the Participants, Submitted by Mrs. M. Sussman & Alan Bloebaum, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 38)
      - Speakers, Panelists, Biographical Information, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 39)
      - Speeches, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 40)
      - Workshops, General Correspondence, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 41)
      - General: Lists, Mimeos, Programs, Forms, etc., 1971 (Box 40, Folder 42)
    - Annual Meeting 1970
      - Affiliation Committee Meeting, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 43)
      - Comments on the Meeting, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 44)
      - Distinguished Guest Speaker, Senator Joseph D. Tydings, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 45)
      - Executive Directors and Chief Executive Officer, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 46)
      - Expenses and Reimbursements, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 47)
      - Dr. Guttmacher's Speech, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 48)
      - Membership Plenary Session, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 49)
      - PP Attorneys, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 50)
      - Regional Council Meeting, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 51)
      - Report of the Department of Training to the Annual Meeting of PPFA, Inc., 1970 (Box 40, Folder 52)
      - Workshop for the Affiliate Executive Directors, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 53)
      - General: Lists, Mimeos, etc., 1970 (Box 40, Folder 54)
    - Annual Meeting 1969
      - Affiliation Committee, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 55)
      - Board of Directors, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 56)
      - By Laws Committee, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 57)
      - Community Affairs Committee, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 58)
      - Executive Committee, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 59)
      - Executive Directors Council, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 60)
      - Expansion and Policy Committee, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 61)
      - Membership Meeting, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 62)
      - Nominating Committee, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 63)
      - News Media Correspondence, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 64)
      - "Objectives of Planned Parenthood," Guest Panel and Luncheon, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 65)
      - PP Attorneys, 1969-70 (Box 40, Folder 66)
      - Press Releases, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 67)
      - Regional Council Meeting, 1969-70 (Box 40, Folder 68)
      - Special Guests, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 69)
      - Special Workshops, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 70)
      - Speeches, Remarks, Sanger Award Text, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 71)
      - General: Lists, Mimeos, etc., 1969 (Box 40, Folder 72)
    - Annual Meeting 1968
      - Affiliation, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 73)
      - Executive Directors' Council, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 74)
      - Expansion and Policy, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 75)
      - Lawyers, 1967-68 (Box 40, Folder 76)
      - Legislative, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 77)
      - Membership Meetings, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 78)
      - Regional Council Meetings, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 79)
      - Regional Representatives, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 80)
      - Symposium and Luncheon, 1968-69 (Box 40, Folder 81)
      - Regrets, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 82)
      - Workshops
        - Affiliates, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 1)
        - I & E, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 2)
        - Volunteers, 1968-69 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Alan Guttmacher, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - General: Lists, etc., 1968 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Annual Meeting 1967
      - Affiliation Committee, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Regional Council Meetings, 1966-67 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Affiliate Volunteer Workshop, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Executive Directors Council, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Expansion and Policy Committee, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Annual Luncheon, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Membership, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - Summary Statement by Paul H. Todd, Jr., 1967 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Fund Raising Workshop, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Legislative Meeting, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 15)
      - PP Attorneys, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - Profile Panel, "Five Million Women," 1967 (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - Press Releases, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - Professional Staff (Affiliates), 1967 (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - Student Panel, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - Uniform Accounting, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 21)
      - Text of Addresses, Discussions, Remarks, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 22)
      - General: Lists, etc., 1967 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Annual Meeting 1966
      - Organizations Participating in Meeting, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 24)
      - General Correspondence, 1965-67 (Box 41, Folder 25)
      - Affiliation Committee Meeting, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 26)
      - Banquet Invitations, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 27)
      - Expansion and Policy Committee, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 28)
      - Lawyers Meeting, Legislative Meeting, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 29)
      - Meeting of Regional Representatives, Chairmen and Directors, Minutes, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 30)
      - Membership Meeting, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 31)
      - Regional Council Meetings, 1968, [MISSING] (Box 41)
      - Organizations Participating in Meeting, 1966, [MISSING] (Box 41)
      - Press Releases, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 32)
      - General Miscellaneous, Lists, 1966-67 (Box 41, Folder 33)
      - Professional Staff Meeting, 1966-67 (Box 41, Folder 34)
      - Professional Staff Workshop Discussions, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 35)
      - Symposium: "Birth Control and Status of Women," 1966-67 (Box 41, Folder 36)
      - Symposium: "Family Planning Action," 1966-67 (Box 41, Folder 37)
      - United Nations Reception, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 38)
      - Text of Addresses, Debates, Remarks, Symposium, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 39)
      - Symposium: Population and Food Session, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - U.S. Congressmen, Acknowledgements, Regrets, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - U.S. Senators' Acknowledgements, Regrets, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Annual Meeting and Banquet, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Annual Meeting, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - DAIS: Biographies, 1960-66 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - AFG, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Participating Organizations Invited to Annual Meeting, (F. Liosi), 1966 (Box 42, Folder 8-9)
      - Invitees to the U.N. Reception, Annual Meeting (F. Liosi), 1966 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Invitations, Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Annual Meeting 1965
      - Banquet, Speaker Invitations, 1965-66 (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Membership Meeting, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - Banquet, Miscellaneous Invitations, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 14)
      - Expansion and Policy Committee Meeting, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 15)
      - Commerce and Industry Meeting, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 16)
      - A Meeting, Michael Harrington, Luncheon, Poverty, Family Planning, and Great Society, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 17)
      - Professional Staff Meeting, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 18)
      - Regional Meetings, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 19)
      - Review Committee Meeting, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 20)
      - A Meeting, Symposium: "Education on Population and Birth Control," 1965 (Box 42, Folder 21)
      - Evaluation Reports, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 22)
      - Press Releases, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 23)
      - General, Miscellaneous Lists, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 24)
      - Dr. Guttmacher's Material, 1964-65 (Box 42, Folder 25)
      - Annual Meeting, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Annual Meeting 1964
      - Banquet
        - Invitations, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 27)
        - Speaker, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 28)
      - Deverell Luncheon, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 29)
      - Dr. Murray Grant Luncheon at MEmbership Meeting, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 30)
      - Membership Meeting, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 31)
      - Professional Staff Meeting, 1963-64 (Box 42, Folder 32)
      - Regional Breakfast, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 33)
      - Symposium, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 34)
      - Professional Staff Evaluation, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 35)
      - Press Releases, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 36)
      - General, Miscellaneous Lists, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Annual Meeting, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Annual Meeting 1963
      - General Correspondence, 1962-63 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - General, Misc. Lists, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Membership Meeting, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Press Releases, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Professional Staff Meeting, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Symposium, 1963-64 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Annual Meeting 1962
      - Banquet, Speaker, C. A. Herter, 1962-63 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - Conference: Economic Consequences, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - Invitations, General, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - Membership Meeting, 1961-69 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - Men's Committee, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Professional Staff Meeting, Attendance Record, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - Professional Staff Meeting, 1962-63 (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - A Meeting, Evaluation, Professional Staff Meeting, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - Symposium: Public Welfare, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 17)
      - Press Releases, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 18)